Guide to the Gerhard Casper, President of Stanford University, Papers SC0672
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- President's records, 1993-1994; Accession ARCH-1996-138
  - Students, Miscellaneous, 1993-1994; ST 1 (Box 14)
  - Student Groups, Miscellaneous, 1993-1994; ST 1.1 (Box 14)
  - Haas Public Service Center, 1993-1994; ST 3.29 (Box 14)
  - Mail Log-Six volumes, 1993-1994 (Box 14)
  - Tanner Lecture material from 1982 forward, 1993-1994 (Box 15)
  - American Law Inst. material 1992/93/94, 1993-1994 (Box 15)
  - Hoover Dir Search, 1993-1994 (Box 16)
- President's records, 1995-1996; Accession ARCH-1998-129
  - University Committee on Minority Issues 1987 (Box 1)
  - Studen t letters to President Casper in 1992 about "need-blind" admissions policy (Box 1)
  - Jean Fetter: Materials on Multicultural Development 1989 - 1994 (Box 1)
  - Cabinet Committee on Budget and Strategic Planning Budget Plans 1/17/92 (Box 1)
  - Tresidder Memorial Union Board 7/80 - 3/97 (Box 1)
  - University Library Council 4/73 - 11/93 (Box 1)
  - From Jean Fetter's desk: Board of Trustees 1991/92 few misc items/notes (Box 1)
  - Soucek & Halcion: Univ. Policy on how to handle the controversy, by C. Lang 2/16/94 (Box 2)
  - Soucek letters on Halcion - William Dement's office 2/94-4/97 (Box 2)
  - Dean Korn's office 6/93 - 2/95 (Box 2)
  - Mike Roster's office 2/94 - 11/94 (Box 2)
  - Regina Casper's office 4/93-10/95 (Box 2)
  - Gerhard Casper's office 6 file folders 3/93 - 11/96 (Box 2)
  - Provost's Office, 10/95 - 5/96; AA 1 (Box 3)
  - Dean of the Chapel, 9/95 - 7/96; AA 1.8 (Box 3)
  - Stanford Graduate Fellowships, 6/96 - 7/96; AA 1.12 (Box 3)
  - Graduate Studies, 6/94 - 8/96; AA 1.13 (Box 3)
  - Graduate Students, special: 5/5/95-11/28/96; AA 1.13.2 (Box 3)
  - Emeriti, 9/95 - 7/96; AA 2.2 (Box 3)
  - Tenure, 9/95 - 8/96; AA 2.3 (Box 3)
  - Faculty/acad appoint's policies, 12/22/1995 only; AA 2.3.2 (Box 3)
  - Faculty Affirmative Action, 94/96 plan & 10/17/94 doc; AA 2.3.3 (Box 3)
  - Sabbatical Leave policy, 9/95 - 1/96; AA 2.6.7 (Box 3)
  - Teaching Loan Policy, 11/95 - 6/96; AA 2.6.8 (Box 3)
  - Faculty Development (general), 9/95 - 8/96; AA 2.7 (Box 3)
  - Fellows of the University, 2/96 - 5/96; AA 2.9 (Box 3)
  - Teaching/Research Assistantsa, 12/95 - 6/96; AA 2.11 (Box 3)
  - Visiting Faculty, 11/26/95 only-Nussbaum; AA 2.12 (Box 3)
  - Undergraduate Issues, 9/95 - 8/96; AA 3 (Box 3)
  - Accreditation, 11/95 - 1/96; AA 3.4 (Box 3)
  - Culture, Ideas/Values, 9/95 - 4/96; AA 3.5.1 (Box 3)
  - Continuing Education, 9/95 - 6/96; AA 3.6 (Box 3)
  - Instructional Technology (cable tv), 5/95 - 5/96; AA 3.9.1 (Box 3)
  - Summer Session, 9/95 - 7/96; AA 3.16 (Box 3)
  - Sophomore Seminars, 8/95 - 8/96; AA 3.18.2 (Box 3)
  - Comparative Studies in Race/Ethni', 1/29/96 only; PAA 4.1 (Box 3)
  - Humanities/Sciences, School of, 9/95 - 8/96; AA 4.1 (Box 3)
  - Humanities Center, 11/95 - 8/96; AA 4.1.1/2 (Box 3)
  - King, Martin Luther Papers, 3/94 - 3/95; AA 4.1.1/3 (Box 3)
  - Anthropology Dept, 10/95 - 6/96; AA 4.1.5 (Box 3)
  - Architecure/Planning-Academic, 11/95 - 6/96; AA 4.1.7 (Box 3)
  - Applied Physics, 10/95 - 6/96; AA 4.1.8 (Box 3)
  - Art Department, 12/95 - 8/96; AA 4.1.9 (Box 3)
  - Chemistry Department, 9/95 - 7/96; AA 4.1.13 (Box 3)
  - Classics Deppartment, 10/95 - 7/96; AA 4.1.14 (Box 3)
  - Communication Department-academic, 11/29/95 & 6/24/96; AA 4.1.15 (Box 3)
  - Computer Science Department, 10/95 - 7/96; AA 4.1.17 (Box 3)
  - Drama Department, 9/95 - 8/96; AA 4.1.18 (Box 3)
  - Economics Department, 10/95 - 8/96; AA 4.1.20 (Box 3)
  - Center for Economic Policy Research, 9/95 - 5/96; AA 4.1.20/1 (Box 3)
  - English Department, 9/95 - 5/96; AA 4.1.21 (Box 3)
  - French and Italian Department, 4/22/96 - 8/23/96; AA 4.1.22 (Box 4)
  - German Department, 10/23/95 - 6/3/96; AA 4.1.24 (Box 4)
  - History Department, 9/15/95 - 8/7/97; AA 4.1.25 (Box 4)
  - Human Biology Program, 10/2/95 only; AA 4.1.26 (Box 4)
  - Mathematics Department, 10/3/95 - 8/15/96; AA 4.1.27 (Box 4)
  - Hopkins Marine Station, 11/15/95 - 6/21/96; AA 4.1.28 (Box 4)
  - Music Department, 10/18/95 - 8/26/96; AA 4.1.29 (Box 4)
  - Athletics-also confidential CR folder, 9/95 - 8/29/96; AA 4.1.30 (Box 4)
  - Football games, 9/94 - 8/96; AA 4.1.30/1 (Box 4)
  - Rose Bowl, 2/7/96 only; AA 4.1.30/2 (Box 4)
  - Athletics Board of Directors, 10/2/95 - 2/14/96; AA 4.1.30/3 (Box 4)
  - Philosophy Department, 9/95 - 5/96; AA 4.1.32 (Box 4)
  - Physics Department, 12/95 - 8/96; AA 4.1.33 (Box 4)
  - Political Science Department, 10/95 - 7/1/96; AA 4.1.34 (Box 4)
  - Psychology Department-Academic, 9/12/95 - 8/28/96; AA 4.1.35 (Box 4)
  - Slavic Department, 7/11/95 - 5/2/96; AA 4.1.38 (Box 4)
  - Sociology Department, 12/14/95 - 10/4/96; AA 4.1.40 (Box 4)
  - Spanish & Portuguese Department, 9/25/95 - 8/20/96; AA 4.1.41 (Box 4)
  - Statistics, 10/19/95 - 5/6/96; AA 4.1.42 (Box 4)
  - Religious Studies Department, 5/8/96 - 6/24/96; AA 4.1.47 (Box 4)
  - S. Center for Res. on Econ.Dev/Policy, 9/19/95 - 5/22/96; AA 4.1.48 (Box 4)
  - Graduate School of Business, 9/5/95 - 8/20/96; AA 4.2 (Box 4)
  - School of Earth Sciences, 10/6/95 - 6/24/96; AA 4.3 (Box 4)
  - School of Engineering, 8/15/95 - 8/16/96; AA 4.4 (Box 4)
  - Elec. Engineering Department, 2/28/96 chron; AA 4.4.5 (Box 4)
  - Operations Research, 11/20/95 - 11/28/95; AA 4.4.10 (Box 4)
  - Civil Engineering, 4/6/95 only; AA 4.4.12 (Box 4)
  - School of Education, 5/24/95 - 8/27/96; AA 4.5 (Box 4)
  - Hoover Institution, General, 9/95 - 8/96; AA 4.9 (Box 5)
  - Hoover Inst Board of Overseers, 9/95 - 12/95; AA 4.9.1 (Box 5)
  - China US Relations, Prog on, 8/95 - 9/96; AA 4.10.3 (Box 5)
  - Center for Int'l Security/Arms Control, 10/28/94 - 7/96; AA 4.10.6 (Box 5)
  - Latin American Studies, Center for, 1/31/96 - 5/2/96; AA 4.11 (Box 5)
  - Russian/East Europ.Studies Center, 3/12/96 - 6/17/96; AA 4.11.1 (Box 5)
  - Stanford Libraries, 2/16/95 - 7/26/96; AA 4.12 (Box 5)
  - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center, 7/13/95-8/29/96; AA 4.13 (Box 5)
  - Title? Found in bottom of file cab, AA 4.14 (Box 5)
  - 7/1/88 Weber (Libraries) to Rosse re retiremt., ditto (Box 5)
  - 10/17/89Herrington/Suppes/trailer for Webster, ditto (Box 5)
  - Center for the Study of Language, 1/6/88-6/21/96; AA 4.14.1 (Box 5)
  - Law School, 11/93- 8/96; AA 4.15 (Box 5)
  - Info. Tech. Systems/Services, 9/95 - 8/96; AA 4.22 (Box 5)
  - Awards/Prizes Miscellaneous, 9/95 - 8/96; AA 5 (Box 6)
  - President's Scholars, 9/95 - 8/96; AA 5.3 (Box 6)
  - Gold Spike Award, 2/96 - 3/96; AA 5.26 (Box 6)
  - Grant/Scholarships, Misc., 9/95 - 8/96; AA 6 (Box 6)
  - Scholarships Misc, 9/95 - 8/96; AA 7 (Box 6)
  - Fellowships Misc, 11/95 - 7/96; AA 8 (Box 6)
  - Fulbright Fellowship, 12/95 - 5/96; AA 8.16 (Box 6)
  - Guggenheim Memorial Fellowship, Fellows from 1974-1989; AA 8.17 (Box 6)
  - Knight Fellowships, 6/92 - 5/96; AA 8.25 (Box 6)
  - Terman Fellows, 12/95 - 6/96; AA 8.30 (Box 6)
  - Harry Camp Memorial Lectures, 12/13/94; AA 9.7 (Box 6)
  - Tanner Lectures, 11/94 -6/96; AA 9.19 (Box 6)
  - Endowed Chairs, 4/95 - 7/22/96; AA 10 (Box 6)
  - Visiting Professors Misc, 12/15/95 only; AA 10.59 (Box 6)
  - Stanford Miscellaneous, 10/95 - 8/96; AD 1 (Box 6)
  - Stanford Historical Society, 10/1/95; AD 1.2 (Box 6)
  - Signature/Resolutions/authority pol., 5/95 - 9/95; AD 1.6.5 (Box 6)
  - Disability Resources, 5/2/96 - 5/15/96; AD 2.11 (Box 6)
  - Alcoholism/drugs, 11/10/95 only; AD 2.15/1 (Box 6)
  - Sexual Harassment, Not archived; AD 2/15/2 (Box 6)
  - Misuse of Stanford Name, 11/21/95 only; AD 2.17 (Box 6)
  - ROTC, 12/95 - 5/96; AD 2.26 (Box 6)
  - Honor code/fundamental standard, 10/95 - 7/96; AD 3.10 (Box 6)
  - Casper/President's office (personal), 9/95 - 8/96; AD 4 (Box 6)
  - President's house, staff, car, 10/94 - 8/96; AD 4.7 (Box 6)
  - University Cabinet, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 4.13 (Box 6)
  - Academic Secretary, 9/14/95 only; AD 4.14 (Box 6)
  - General Counsel (Legal), 9/95 - 8/96; AD 4.19 (Box 7)
  - Correspondence, General, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 4.20 (Box 7)
  - Jacques Chessex-Asian Sex tours, pedophile issue 1995; AD 4.20.1 (Box 7)
  - News Clippings/Editorials, 9/95 - 2/96; AD 4.20.1 (Box 7)
  - Condolence Letters, 9/95 -8/96; AD 4.20.2 (Box 7)
  - Congratulatory Letters, 10/95 - 5/96; AD 4.20.3 (Box 7)
  - Invitations, 3/95 - 5/96; AD 4.20.4 (Box 7)
  - Appreciation letters, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 4.20.4/1 (Box 7)
  - Invitations, general, 2/8/95 - 8/31/96; AD 4.20.4/2 (Box 7)
  - Nonsense file, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 4.20.5 (Box 7)
  - Recommendation/Search Ltr's, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 4.20.6 (Box 8)
  - Recommendation Ltr's, Students, 10/95 - 5/96; AD 4.20.6/1 (Box 8)
  - Complaint letters, 9/95 - 6/14/96; AD 4.20.7 (Box 8)
  - Solicitations, general/misc, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 4.20.8 (Box 8)
  - Harvard University Press, Not archived; AD 4.20.9 (Box 8)
  - Univ. Comm. Diversity Myth Campaign, 1996; AD 4.22 (Box 8)
  - University Communications, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 4.22 (Box 8)
  - Formerly Ombudsman, 10/95 - 6/96; AD 6 (Box 8)
  - Admissions, 9/95 - 7/12/96; AD 8.1 (Box 8)
  - Admissions Cases, 11/8/95 only; AD 8.1.2 (Box 8)
  - Dean of Student Affairs, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 8.8 (Box 8)
  - Overseas Studies Programs, Misc, 10/19/95 - 6/19/96; AD 8.11 (Box 8)
  - Overseas studies (Stanford in France), 12/5/95 only; AD 8.11.3 (Box 8)
  - Overseas studies (SU in Germany), 9/95 - 6/28/96; AD 8.11.4/2 (Box 8)
  - Financial Aid, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 8.12 (Box 9)
  - Housing, Faculty, Staff, Emeriti, 9/95 - 8/2/96; AD 8.18 (Box 9)
  - Hanna Honeycomb House, 10/95 - 4/96; AD 8.18.2 (Box 9)
  - Lake House, Nothing in there to archive; AD 8.18.3 (Box 9)
  - Buck Estate, 9/12/95 only; AD 8.18.4 (Box 9)
  - Fraternities/Sororities, Selective: 5/91 - 8/96; AD 8.18.8 (Box 9)
  - Housing/dining-student, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 8.18.11 (Box 9)
  - Residential education, 9/95 - 8/15/96; AD 8.18.13 (Box 9)
  - Bursar, Registrar, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 8.21 (Box 9)
  - Black Affairs, 9/95- - 2/16/96; AD 9.1 (Box 9)
  - Chicano Affairs, Not archived; AD 9.2 (Box 9)
  - Grape Boycott, Not archived; AD 9.2.1 (Box 9)
  - Native American Indian Affairs, 9/95 - 3/5/96; AD 9.3 (Box 9)
  - Culture and Cultures, 2/8/96 - 6/4/96; AD 9.5 (Box 9)
  - Multicultural Development-- use AD 6, 9/95 - 7/12/96; AD 9.6 (Box 9)
  - Spec. materials JHF collected for GC's article on diversity--6/96, AD 9.6.3 (Box 9)
  - Affirmative Action, Student, 9/95 - 8/1/96; AD 9.6.3 (Box 9)
  - Personnel -- Michael Tsai, 12/95; AD 10 (Box 9)
  - Personnel Services, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 10 (Box 9)
  - Employment Inquiries/Requests, 9/95 - 8/8/96; AD 10.1 (Box 9)
  - Mentoring Program, 10/27/95; AD 10.4 (Box 9)
  - Outdoor Art Committee, 9/95 - 7/19/96; AD 10.7.4 (Box 9)
  - United Stanford Employees, 2/96 - 6/96; AD 10.7.8 (Box 9)
  - Personnel Policies, 10/12/95 - 8/14/96; AD 10.8 (Box 9)
  - Grievance Issues-Faculty Staff, 10/6/94 - 8/96; AD 10.8.10/1 (Box 9)
  - Grievance Issues - Student, 12/13/94 - 1/9/96; AD 10.8/10/3 (Box 9)
  - Retirement, 2/22/96 Ret. redesign-8/96; AD 10.8.17 (Box 9)
  - Salaries, 9/95 - 6/96; AD 10.8.19 (Box 10)
  - Tuition Benefit Plan-some for '99, 9/95-8/5/96; AD 10.8.22 (Box 10)
  - Operation and Maintenance, 12/6/95 - 5/16/96; AD 11.4 (Box 10)
  - Environmental Health and Safety, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 11.4.1 (Box 10)
  - Campus Security-not archived, Nazi stuff '95 Abbas Rahal; AD 11.6 (Box 10)
  - Campus Security, 9/25/95 - 5/10/96; AD 11.6 (Box 10)
  - Commencement stuff back to '95, Do not Archive; AD 11.7.2 (Box 10)
  - Stanford Events, 9/95 - 6/96; AD 11.7.5/1 (Box 10)
  - Lively Arts, 12/20/94 - 6/7/96; AD 11.7.5/2 (Box 10)
  - Freshman stuff, 9/21/95 - 6/4/96; AD 11.7.7 (Box 10)
  - Media, External, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 11.8 (Box 10)
  - Copyright Policy, Do not Archive; AD 11.8.1 (Box 10)
  - Stanford University Press, 9/95 - 8/96; AD 11.8.9 (Box 10)
  - Surveys/Questionaires, 7/95 - 8/96; AD 11.8.10 (Box 10)
  - Media, Internal, Stanford Review blitz of '96; AD 11.8.11 (Box 10)
  - Media, Internal, 2/95 - 8/96; AD 11.8.11 (Box 10)
  - Stanford Observer, 10/4/95 only; AD 11.8.11/3 (Box 10)
  - Business and Finance, Nothing to archive; AD 12.2 (Box 10)
  - CFO, 9/95 - 2/5/96; AD 12.2/1 (Box 10)
  - VP of Finance, 10/12/95 - 8/19/96; AD 12.2/2 (Box 10)
  - Administrative Resources, 10/24/95 - 8/29/96; AD 12.2/3 (Box 10)
  - Stanford Management Co., 9/95 - 8/96; AD 12.3 (Box 10)
  - Internal Auditing, 9/95 - 3/11/96; AD 12.4 (Box 11)
  - Budget, 11/12/95 - 8/6/96; AD 12.5 (Box 11)
  - Tuition, 10/1/95 - 1/12/96; AD 12.5.4 (Box 11)
  - Conflict of Interest/Consulting Pol., 1/19/96 - 7/12/96; AD 12.7.1 (Box 11)
  - Restricted Funds, 10/95 - 1/96; AD 12.9.1 (Box 11)
  - Development, John Ford stuff, 10/95 - 8/96; AD 12.10 (Box 11)
  - Development, Big Picture Planning, 8/31/95 - 8/96; AD 12.10.1 (Box 11)
  - Student Fund raising, senior gift, 6/6 & 6/11/96 only; AD 12.10.2/1 (Box 11)
  - President's Fund, 9/11/95 - 8/17/96; AD 12.10.2/2 (Box 11)
  - The Stanford Fund, 10/6/95 - 8/26/96; AD 12.10.2/3 (Box 11)
  - Matching Gifts, 9/15/95 - 8/8/96; AD 12.10.2/4 (Box 11)
  - Development events, 9/6/95 - 8/8/96; AD 12.10.2/5 (Box 11)
  - Donor Relations, general and misc, 5/93 - 8/96; AD 12.10.2/7 (Box 11)
  - National Resources Program, 9/95 - 4/29/96; AD 12.10.2/8 (Box 11)
  - Asian Relations, General, 2/14/95 - 8/96; AD 12.10.2/9 (Box 11)
  - Bandet, Fred (Box 12)
  - Boething, John E. (Box 12)
  - Boone, George (friend of Ukropina's) (Box 12)
  - Boswell, Jim (moved to Med Dev) (Box 12)
  - Bullis, Richard-partial archive (Box 12)
  - Ginzton, Edward (Box 12)
  - Hemmeter, Christopher (Box 12)
  - Jonsson, Erik and Margaret (Box 12)
  - Koll, Don (Box 12)
  - Montgomery, K. (Box 12)
  - McClatchy, James (newspapers) (Box 12)
  - McCoy, (Buzz) Bowen (Box 12)
  - Noyce, Robert (Box 12)
  - Shorenstein, Walter-to 5/3/96 (Box 12)
  - Speigel, John W. (Box 12)
  - Stewart, Arthur (Box 12)
  - Swig, R. (Box 12)
  - White, William (Hale Kea Farms) (Box 12)
  - Gifts Miscellaneous-Partial archive, 9/94-8/96; AD12.10.3/5-1 (Box 12)
  - Gifts Misc-Arnold Schoenberg Archive, AD12.10.3/5-1 (Box 12)
  - Cook, M/M Paul, AD 12.10.3/5-11.5 (Box 12)
  - Ducommun Foundation, AD 12.10.3/5-18 (Box 12)
  - Dupont/Conoco-Code kept/contents arch, 1/25/91-7/29/96; AD 12.10.3/5-19 (Box 12)
  - Ford Motor Company, AD 12.10.3/5-24 (Box 12)
  - Glenmede Trust (docs are Pew however?, 9/10/92 - 8/23/94; AD 12.10.3/5-26 (Box 12)
  - PG&E-Code kept/contents archived, 7/1/83 - 7/6/94; AD 12.10.3/5-35 (Box 12)
  - Sterling, Wallace (Award), 1993 (use: AA 5.5); AD 12.10.3/5-43 (Box 12)
  - Syntex, AD 12.10.3/5-46 (Box 12)
  - Varian Corporation, 2/84 - 5/93; AD 12.10.3/5-48 (Box 12)
  - Xerox Corp, 12/82 - 12/93; AD 12.10.3/5-49 (Box 12)
  - Corporation/Foundations Misc, Partial: 9/94 - 8/96; AD 12.10.4 (Box 12)
  - Alcoa Foundation, Partial: 7/93-10/95; AD 12.10.4/4 (Box 12)
  - Keck Foundation, Partial: 11/92-7/96; AD 12.10.4/6 (Box 12)
  - ARCS Fdn-Achieve.Rewards/Coll Sci., Partial: 4/94-7/96; AD 12.10.4/10 (Box 12)
  - Boswell Foundation, Code deleted: 10/27/93; AD 12.10.4/21 (Box 12)
  - Chiles Foundation, Partial: 3/5/93-8/21/96; AD 12.10.4/40 (Box 12)
  - Commonwealth Fund, Partial: 5/90-6/96; AD 12.10.4/47 (Box 12)
  - Newhouse Fund (See AD 12.10.4/154), AD 12.10.4/54 (Box 12)
  - Danforth Foundation (Harbison), AD 12.10.4/55 (Box 12)
  - Dreyfus Foundation, AD 12.10.4/60 (Box 12)
  - Exxon, Partial: 10/92-4/96; AD 12.10.4/67 (Box 13)
  - Ford Foundation, Partial: 10/94-8/96; AD 12.10.4/71 (Box 13)
  - General Electric, Partial: 12/88-7/96; AD 12.10.4/78 (Box 13)
  - Getty Trust Fund (et. al.), Partial: 7/93-5/96; AD 12.10.4/80 (Box 13)
  - Hearst Foundation, Code deleted: 11/82-6/95; AD 12.10.4/87 (Box 13)
  - James Irvine Foundation, Partial: 9/94 - 4/96; AD12.10.4/103 (Box 13)
  - Robt. Wood. Johnson Foundation, Partial: 10/29/93-5/6/96; AD12.10.4/107 (Box 13)
  - Kaiser Foundation, Code deleted: 4/94; AD 12.10.4/110 (Box 13)
  - W. K. Kellogg Fdn, Code deleted: 12/95-8/97; AD12.10.4/112 (Box 13)
  - Koret Foundation, Partial: 3/94-8/96; AD12.10.4/115 (Box 13)
  - Kresge Foundation, Code deleted: 1/93-3/94; AD12.10.4/117 (Box 13)
  - The Leakey Foundation, Code deleted: 10/28/93 chron; AD12.10.4/118 (Box 13)
  - The Henry Luce Foundation, Partial: 9/30/93-3/96; AD12.10.4/126 (Box 13)
  - MacArthur Foundation, Partial: 9/30/93-4/28/96; AD12.10.4/130 (Box 13)
  - Lucille Markey Charitable Trust, Not archived in '98; AD12.10.4/131 (Box 13)
  - Mellon, Andrew Foundation, Partial: 9/20/93-6/96; AD12.10.4/139 (Box 13)
  - NEH Nat'l.Endow.for the Humanities, Code deleted: 10/93-5/7/96; AD12.10.4/152 (Box 13)
  - Newhouse Fund, Partial: 9/30/94-6/19/96; AD12.10.4/154 (Box 13)
  - Norcliff Foundation, AD12.10.4/155 (Box 13)
  - UPS United Parcel Serv. Foundation, Code deleted:11/17/94-7/8/96; AD12.10.4/156 (Box 13)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, Partial: 11/93-6/96; AD12.10.4/184 (Box 13)
  - San Francisco Foundation, Partial: 1/21/92-7/18/96; AD12.10.4/192 (Box 13)
  - Schlumberger Foundation, Code deleted: 3/28/84-7/95; AD12.10.4/197 (Box 13)
  - Shell Oil Co. Foundation, Partial: 1/21/94-3/96; AD12.10.4/200 (Box 13)
  - Sloan, Alfred P. Foundation, Partial: 10/93-8/5/96; AD12.10.4/204 (Box 13)
  - Spencer Foundation, Partial: 9/93-8/96; AD12.10.4/211 (Box 13)
  - Alex. von Humboldt Stiftung, Partial: 12/93-8/96; AD12.10.4/242 (Box 13)
  - Tinker Foundation, Code deleted: July/Aug '96; AD12.10.4/246 (Box 13)
  - Times Mirror Foundation, Code deleted: 5/95-6/95; AD12.10.4/248 (Box 13)
  - Harry Truman Scholarships, Partial: 10/93-3/96; AD12.10.4/251 (Box 13)
  - Sherman Fairchild Foundation, Code deleted: 5/96 only; AD12.10.4/271 (Box 13)
  - Research Corporation, Code deleted: 6/84-3/95; AD12.10.4/288 (Box 13)
  - Union Oil Co., Code deleted: 5/31/95 only; AD12.10.4/302 (Box 13)
  - Pew Charitable Trusts, Partial: 5/25/93-8/12/96; AD12.10.4/303 (Box 13)
  - Grover Herman Foundation, Code deleted: 8/30/94 only; AD12.10.4/305 (Box 13)
  - United Way of Santa Clara (CHAD), Code deleted: 9/95-5/96; AD12.10.8 (Box 13)
  - Tech., Licensing, Patents, Copyrights, 6/95-8/96; AD 12.11 (Box 13)
  - Land and Buildings, 9/95 - 7/96; AD 12.14 (Box 13)
  - Names for Stanford places, 11/21-12/11/95; AD 12.14.5 (Box 13)
  - Buildings, space, land use, etc, 3/12/96 only; AD 12.14.7 (Box 13)
  - Museum/Art Galleries, etc., 10/95-8/96; AD 12.14.7/1 (Box 13)
  - Prof. Bernard Andrea visit 1996, 6/95-1/96; AD 12.14.7/1 (Box 13)
  - Athletics (space, 4/25/96-6/17/96; AD12.14.7/2 (Box 14)
  - Stanford Bookstore, 1/27/95-8/96; AD12.14.7/5 (Box 14)
  - Center for Clinical Sciences Research, 11/29/95-5/3/96; AD12.14.7/10 (Box 14)
  - Facilities/Planning/Univ.Architect, 7/20/95-8/96; AD12.14.7/29 (Box 14)
  - Faculty Club, 9/1/95-8/96; AD12.14.7/30 (Box 14)
  - Jasper Ridge Biological Preserve, 12/9/95 & 5/16/96 only; AD12.14.7/43 (Box 14)
  - Memorial Church/Campus Ministries, 10/95-5/13/96; AD12.14.7/50 (Box 14)
  - Parking/Transportation, 9/18/95-6/3/96; AD12.14.7/53 (Box 14)
  - Tresidder Memorial Union Building, 4/17/96-8/19/96; AD12.14.7/64 (Box 14)
  - Accounting, 3/96-7/96; AD 12.15 (Box 14)
  - Conferences Miscellaneous, 1/94-8/96; AD 13.10.1 (Box 14)
  - Sch. of Earth Sci. Advisory Board, 1/16/96-7/96; AD 13.10.5/2 (Box 14)
  - Sch. of Engr. Advisory Council, 3/19/96 chron only; AD 13.10.5/7 (Box 14)
  - Sch. of Business Advisory Board, 10/95-11/7/96; AD 13.10.5/8 (Box 14)
  - Univ/Industry Relations-Gibbons stuff, 1/96-6/17/96; AD 15 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Relations-General, 8/17/95-8/20/96; AL 1 (Box 14)
  - Alum/Letters to Parents, 9/23/95-5/1/96; AL 1.1 (Box 14)
  - Parents Club (Mothers Club), 4/7/95-6/6/96 chron; AL 1.1/1 (Box 14)
  - Letters, Alum/Students, 8/95 - 1/8/96; AL 1.2 (Box 14)
  - Alum. Corresp. General, 3/95-8/96; AL 1.3 (Box 14)
  - Annual Grad ltrs/responses, 9/95-8/96; AL 1.4 (Box 14)
  - Homecoming/Reunion/alum events, 2/28/95-8/5/96; AL 1.7 (Box 14)
  - Class Reunions, 10/94-8/16/96; AL 1.8 (Box 14)
  - Stanford Magazine, 9/95-1/8/96; AL 1.12 (Box 14)
  - Stanford Associates, 2/29/96 & 7/22/96 only; AL 2 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Association-General, 9/22/95-8/27/96; AL 3 (Box 14)
  - Bowman Alum, 3/14/96-8/9/96; AL 4 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Giving-General, 10/17/95-6/18/96; AL 5 (Box 14)
  - BoT Misc., 9/95-8/96; B 1 (Box 15)
  - BoT Correspondence, 3/6/96-7/96; B 2 (Box 15)
  - Trustee Appointments/Resignations, 9/18/95-7/26/96; B 12 (Box 15)
  - BoT Committee's (Several), 8/16/94-6/96; B 14 (Box 15)
  - BoT Sub Comm. on Development, 8/24/94-4/22/96; B 14.3.1 (Box 15)
  - BoT Comm. on Finance & Admin., 5/16/94-4/22/96; B 14.4 (Box 15)
  - BoT Comm. on Land and Building plan, 9/14/95-7/26/96; B 14.6 (Box 15)
  - BoT Comm. on Nominations, 9/26/94-7/12/95; B 14.7 (Box 15)
  - BoT Comm. onMinority Alum Relations, 8/19/94-6/96; B 14.11 (Box 15)
  - BoT Comm. on Alum/External Affairs, 4/19, 22, 5/9/96 chrons only; B 14.12 (Box 15)
  - Academic Council, 10/18/95-1/11/96; C 1 (Box 15)
  - Senate of the Academic Council, 10/95-6/96; C 2 (Box 15)
  - Senate of the Academic Council Corresp, 9/25 & 10/31/95 only; C 2.1 (Box 15)
  - Senate of the Acad Council - Report, 12/12/95 & 12/19/95 only; C 2.4 (Box 15)
  - Acad Council - Advisory Board, 9/11/95 - 8/5/96; C 3 (Box 15)
  - Steering Comm of the Acad Council, 9/27/95 - 1/11/96; C 4.1 (Box 15)
  - Committee on Committees (To: C 2), 11/27/95-3/13/96; C 4.2 (Box 15)
  - Comm. on Develop.Ext Aff/Alum Aff, 10/9/95 - 2/12/96; C 4.4 (Box 15)
  - CAA Comm on acad Achieve/Appraisal, Dead Week question 95/96; C 5.1 (Box 15)
  - Gore/Dinkelspiel Awards, 6/4/96 only, provost copy; C 5.1.3 (Box 15)
  - Rhodes/Marshall, 12/12/95-3/8/96; C 5.1.4 (Box 15)
  - CUE Comm on U. G. Education, 11/8/95 - 12/11/95; C 5.7.1 (Box 15)
  - CTTL Comm on Tech in Teach/Learning, 8/95-5/96; C 5.7.2 (Box 15)
  - University Committees, 10/31/95-5/23/96; C 6 (Box 15)
  - Committee of 15, 3/96-6/14/96; C 6.1 (Box 15)
  - Comm on Land/Bldg Development, 9/27/95-9/19/96Sept; C 6.6 (Box 15)
  - Comm of Faculty/Staff Benefits, 10/19/95-10/96 (October); C 6.15 (Box 15)
  - Government relations, general, 9/95 - 8/96; G 1 (Box 16)
  - CA State government, general, 9/15/95 - 8/8/96; G 1.2 (Box 16)
  - CA Post Secondary Ed. Comm., 9/95 only 2 documents; G 1.3.5 (Box 16)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 9/8/95 - 3/22/96; G 2.3 (Box 16)
  - U. S. Government Relations, 9/95 - 8/9/96; G 3 (Box 16)
  - Defense Department, 9/26/95 - 6/12/96; G 3.7 (Box 16)
  - Department of Energy, 6/25 and 7/22/96 only; G 3.7.2 (Box 16)
  - NASA Ames Research, 11/21/95 and 4/15/96 only; G 3.7.4 (Box 16)
  - Office of Health and Human Services, 10/6/95 & 4/10/96 only; G 3.8.1 (Box 16)
  - Nat'l Institutes of Health, 4/12/96 - 6/19/96; G 3.8.2 (Box 16)
  - Department of Education, 9/95 - 7/96; G 3.8.3 (Box 16)
  - President of the United States, 10/95 - 3/20/96; G 3.15 (Box 16)
  - Internal Revenue Service, 9/5/95 & 7/31/96 only; G 3.18.1 (Box 16)
  - National Science Foundation, 9/95 - 8/96; G 3.19 (Box 16)
  - Federal Agencies misc, 1/30/96 only; G 3.29 (Box 16)
  - Local Government, 9/27/95 - 7/12/96; G 4 (Box 16)
  - Foreign Government Relations, 10/25/95 - 6/96; G 5 (Box 16)
  - Congress (CR chron 1/19/96 and CR, 1/24/96 Dennis Browne only; G 6 (Box 16)
  - CA Institute for Federal Policy Research, 9/21/95 - 8/19/96; G 7 (Box 16)
  - Pacific Council on Int'l Policy, 7/95 - 8/96; G 10 (Box 16)
  - United Nations, 8/20 & 26/96 only; G 12 (Box 16)
  - United Stated Senate, 9/95 - 3/19/96; G 13 (Box 16)
  - Medi. Sch. general: includ Niederhuber, 11/30/93-8/96; M 1 (Box 16)
  - Medical School Development, 9/21/95 - 8/15/96; M 2 (Box 16)
  - Med. Sch Executive Committee, 2/6/95-4/19/96; M 3 (Box 16)
  - Dept of Medicine, 1/25/96-7/16/96; M 4 (Box 16)
  - Med Sch Departments Misc, 9/27/95 - 8/28/96; M 5 (Box 16)
  - SHS, general, 10/18/95 only; SHS 2 (Box 16)